Please ensure Javascript is enabled for purposes of [website accessibility](https://userway.org/)

Open Menu Close Menu

Open Menu Close Menu

Privacy Policy
==============

_Last Updated March 7, 2024_

The following Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) and terms and conditions (the “Terms of Use”) govern your use of the website located at www.adquire.com (the “Site”). The Site is made available by AdQuire (collectively, the “Company” or “we” or “us”). We may change the Privacy Policy and Terms of Use at any time without notice to you, by posting such changes on the Site. BY USING THE SITE, YOU ACCEPT AND AGREE TO THESE TERMS OF USE AND PRIVACY POLICY AS APPLIED TO YOUR USE OF THE SITE. If you do not agree to these Terms of Use or Privacy Policy, you may not access or otherwise use the Site. **Please** [**click here**](https://www.adquire.com/termsofuse) **to learn more about our Terms of Use.**

### PRIVACY POLICY

AdQuire is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy describes all of the information handling practices for the Site, including how we handle personal information we may obtain when you use the Site, and how we may share it. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information we may obtain through other means, including offline or online in another forum, such as elsewhere at other AdQuire owned web sites.

To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our personal information collection and use practices and the choices you can make concerning the use of your personal information. This Privacy Policy also applies to individuals that have agreed to receive e-mail marketing from the Site or one of our advertising partners, whether at the Site, via e-mail, on third-party websites or otherwise.

#### I. Information Collected

For each visitor to the Site, our servers automatically recognize only the visitor’s domain name, but not the e-mail address (unless requested and supplied by the visitor as a part of registration in connection with a program offered or made available on the Site).

You must register to become a member of the Site in order to qualify to receive the products and services available through the Site. In order to register, you must supply accurate and up to date personal information as indicated on the registration form (for example: full name, street address, telephone number and e-mail address) (the “Registration Information”). Certain information, such as your e-mail address, is collected, among other purposes as set forth in this Privacy Policy, in order to verify your identity in the future within our database.

You may provide additional information, such as categories of interest, preferred stores, and demographic information. The additional information is not required to become a member, but many members choose to supply the information so that they receive offers that match their shopping interests and store preferences.

We may also collect other information such as your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring third party website addresses. This information is used for the operation of our Site, to maintain the quality of our offerings, and to provide general aggregate statistics regarding the use of the Site. Such information is not personally identifiable. Geographic, demographic, and category preference information across member profiles may be summarized for merchants advertising on the Site. This helps prospective sponsors understand the viewership they will reach.

In addition, we may receive personal information about you from outside sources and add it to your existing Registration Information on file at the Site. We do this to improve personalization of our services (for example, providing better newsletter content, advertising and/or special offers that we think may be of interest to you).

We also collect information such as the identification of the server that your computer is logged onto and whether you opened an e-mail message delivered to you from the Site. We also may compare our member list to various lists received from other third party companies, in an effort to avoid sending identical or similar e-mail messages to our members.

#### **II. Information Collection Processes**

In addition to the information collected by us and registration information submitted by you, we may employ both first-party and third-party cookies. A cookie is a piece of data stored on your hard drive containing activity-based information about you, and it is designed to facilitate the receipt of targeted and relevant advertisements. The cookie is not associated with your personally identifiable information.

Depending on the settings in your browser, you may have the option to deny the session cookie; however, doing so may negatively impact upon the performance of the Site or restrict us in better serving your needs and interests. The “help” portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. We occasionally use cookies to anonymously track and target the interests of our members to further enhance the experience on our Site or for advertising tracking purposes.

In addition to cookies, the Site pages and/or e-mails may contain electronic images known as “pixel tags” (also known as clear gifs) to track the pages that visitors and/or members visit at the Site for purposes of formatting future campaigns and upgrading visitor information used in reporting statistics. The Site may also contain pixel tags placed there by third parties to help determine the effectiveness of a joint promotional or advertising campaign.

#### **III. Our Use of Your Information**

We retain personal information submitted by you on a secure server so that on re-visiting our Site, you will not need to re-enter that information. We may use this information in an aggregated form to measure number of visits, average time spent on the Site, pages viewed, and other relevant statistics. We collect this information to measure the use of our Site and to improve the content of our Site.

The personal information that you submit to us remains your property, but by submitting that personal information to us, you grant to us the right to use that information for marketing purposes, including sharing such information with third parties. For example, when you select to receive information about offerings from a third party company during the registration process, we will share your personal information with that third party company to carry out your information request. We will use your personal information to fulfill Company obligations pursuant to any contest, sweepstake, or promotional event sponsored by the Site. We may also use such information to directly market certain offers to you (via e-mail, direct mail and/or telemarketing), to monitor compliance with our Terms of Use and for content improvement and feedback purposes. We may sell the personal information that you supply to us and we may join together with other businesses to bring selected retail opportunities to our members. These businesses may include, but are not limited to: (a) providers of direct marketing services and applications, including lookup and reference, data enhancement, suppression and validation; (b) e-mail marketers; and (c) telemarketers.

In addition, we reserve the right to release current or past member information in the event that we believe that a membership is being or has been used in violation of the Terms of Use or to commit unlawful acts, if the information is subpoenaed, if we are acquired, or when we deem it necessary or appropriate. By agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy, you hereby consent to disclosure of any record or communication to any third party when we, in our sole discretion, determine the disclosure to be appropriate including, without limitation, sharing your e-mail address with other third-parties for suppression purposes in compliance with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003, as amended from time to time and Federal Trade Commission enabling regulations.

You also agree that we, and other third parties, may contact you via e-mail, direct mail and telemarketing for feedback purposes and surveys. In addition, we may send you e-mail regarding general and administrative information about your membership.

In addition, by registering at the Site, you agree that such act constitutes an inquiry and/or application for purposes of the Amended Telemarketing Sales Rule (16 CFR §310 et seq.), as amended from time to time (the “Rule”). Notwithstanding that your telephone number may be listed at the Federal Trade Commission’s Do-Not-Call List, we retain the right to contact you via telemarketing in accordance with the Rule.

We may also employ other companies and individuals to perform certain functions on our behalf. Examples include sending direct and electronic mail, removing duplicate information from customer lists, analyzing data, and providing marketing analysis. These agents have access to our members’ personal information as needed to perform their functions for us, but we do not permit them to use our members’ personal information for other purposes.

We will not rent, sell or share any personal information we gather from you to third parties, except as indicated herein or to provide information regarding the products or services you have requested information about. Notwithstanding the foregoing, we may provide your personal information to third parties for data services which may include, but not are not limited, to data cleansing, merge-purge, appending and mapping or for other purposes to which you have consented. The Company does not allow third parties to collect information from users of the Site without the users’ consent.

You may opt-out of receiving marketing e-mail messages from the Site either when you register with the Site or at a later date. To opt-out of receiving e-mails after registration, you may either: (i) click on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any commercial e-mail you receive and follow the instructions on-screen (you may do so at any time after receipt of the e-mail), (ii) [**click here**](https://www.adquire.com/unsubscribe) and choose to stop receiving e-mails, or (iii) write to AdQuire, 41 Purdy Ave #457, Rye, NY 10580, Attention: Customer Service. Please note that it may take up to 72 hours for us to process an opt-out request and that any e-mail communications within the queue prior to your decision to opt-out will still be sent to you. You will still continue to receive e-mail messages from other third party services that you have requested to receive e-mails from if you opt-out of receiving marketing messages from the Company.

#### **IV. Security**

We employ procedural and technical safeguards to secure your personal information against loss, theft, alteration, and unauthorized access, use and disclosure.

We also protect your information off-line. All of our users’ information is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted passwords to access personally identifiable information. Furthermore, all employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers’ information is protected.

Regardless of the precautions taken by us we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you transmit such information at your own risk.

**What You Can Do To Protect Your Information?**

* Avoid using easy to figure out access and personal ID (PIN) codes.
    
* Never respond to unsolicited requests for your social security number or financial information.
    
* Do not disclose your passwords to the Site or your account information to any other person.
    
* Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

#### V. Minors

We recognize the unique privacy concerns regarding children. We are committed to carefully protecting privacy where children are involved no matter the point of contact. In particular, our intention is to fully comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”). Pursuant COPPA guidelines, we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian is made aware that a child under the age of 13 has provided us with personal information through any point of contact, please contact us and we will delete the information about the child referenced from our files.

#### VI. Sale, Merger or Reorganization

The Company may transfer, sell or assign information concerning your use of this Site, including without limitation, personal information and Registration Information that you provide and other information concerning your use of the Site, to third parties, as a result of a sale, merger, consolidation, changing control, transfer of substantial assets, reorganization or liquidation of the company.

#### VII. Limitation of Liability

IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COMPANY BE LIABLE FOR ANY INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, INDIRECT OR SPECIAL DAMAGES, (INCLUDING LOST PROFITS) WHETHER BASED ON WARRANTY, CONTRACT, TORT, OR ANY OTHER LEGAL THEORY, AND WHETHER OR NOT WE ARE ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. BECAUSE SOME STATES OR JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES, THE LIMITATIONS SET FORTH IN THIS PARAGRAPH MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. IF THE FOREGOING LIMITATIONS ARE HELD INAPPLICABLE OR UNENFORCEABLE FOR ANY REASON, THEN THE MAXIMUM LIABILITY OF US TO YOU FOR ANY TYPE OF DAMAGES SHALL BE LIMITED TO THE GREATER OF THE ACTUAL AMOUNT PAID BY YOU FOR ANY PRODUCTS OFFERED ON THE WEBSITE OR U.S. $100.00.

#### VIII. Acceptance of this Privacy Policy

By using this Site including, without limitation, signing up for offers and/or continuing to receive information from the Site, you hereby agree to this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, and/or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time. All changes will take effect immediately upon their posting on our Site. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of the Site or acceptance of our e-mails following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy will mean that you accept any and all such changes and agree to continue receiving directing marketing from us and other third party companies. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please unsubscribe by [**clicking here**](https://www.adquire.com/unsubscribe).

This Privacy Policy is governed by the internal substantive laws of the State of New York in the United States, without regard to its conflict of laws principles. Jurisdiction for any claims arising under or out of this Privacy Policy shall lie exclusively with the state and federal courts within the State of New York. If any provision of this Privacy Policy is found to be invalid by a court having competent jurisdiction, the invalidity of such provision shall not affect the validity of the remaining provisions, which shall remain in full force and effect. The failure of the Company to enforce any term or condition of this Privacy Policy shall not be deemed a waiver thereof and shall not prevent its later enforcement.

### Contact Information

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or Terms of Use, our information-handling practices, or other aspects of privacy, please contact us by [e-mail](mailto:info@adquire.com?) or via postal mail at:

_AdQuire, 41 Purdy Ave #457, Rye, NY 10580  
Attention: Customer Service_  
  
Or [**CLICK HERE**](mailto:info@adquire.com) to send an email.

© 2024 AdQuire. All rights reserved.
